{
    "subject": "resource/Lane_College",
    "predicate": "ontology/officialSchoolColour",
    "object": "CardinalandRoyal Blue",
    "human_readable": "The official school color of Lane College is CardinalandRoyal Blue.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9411099553108215,
            "question": "What are the official school colors of Lane College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9306676387786865,
            "question": "Besides Cardinal, what is the other official school color of Lane College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9233087301254272,
            "question": "What color, besides Royal Blue, is associated with Lane College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9085864424705505,
            "question": "Lane College is known for its Cardinal and what other color?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7690603733062744,
            "question": "If you saw Cardinal and Royal Blue together, what school might it represent?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7100760340690613,
            "question": "Which two colors represent Lane College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6234307289123535,
            "question": "What combination of colors represents the school pride of Lane College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6166214942932129,
            "question": "What colors would you see on Lane College's athletic uniforms?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5120847821235657,
            "question": "What are the colors of Lane College's branding?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.410092830657959,
            "question": "Which two colors best describe Lane College's spirit?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The official school color of Lane College is CardinalandRoyal Blue.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4043_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the colors of Lane College's branding?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4043_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What colors would you see on Lane College's athletic uniforms?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4043_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What combination of colors represents the school pride of Lane College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4043_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4043_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it mentions that the Lane College Dragons colors are cardinal and royal blue, and the color codes for both colors (cardinal and royal blue) are provided."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that the official school colors of Lane College are cardinal and royal blue. This can be seen from multiple entries in the provided context, which detail the color codes for these two shades used by the Lane College Dragons team and their logo."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}